djawir.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy | djawir Community

* djawir Community recognizes that you care about the personal information that is held about you and how that is used.

* This privacy policy applies to all personal data, submitted by you, to the djawir Community web site.

* By registering to djawir Community you need to submit a chosen name and contact information, more specifically an e-mail address. No extremely personal information, such as Social Security or Credit Card numbers are stored by us.

* djawir Community also stores and reads cookies to and from your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our forums and general website features to recognize your browser for when you return to this web site. By using this website, you agree that both the webserver, and any trusted 3rd party we choose, such as advertising networks, may place a tracking cookie on your machine and access it at any time during your session. In general, cookies are safe and are not a security issue when being used from 'trusted' internet sites, such as djawir Community. For information on how to manage cookies in your browser, please visit [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2)

* Some of our advertising partners use tracking cookies to serve the most relevant ads to you based on your browsing habits. You may opt out of these tracking cookies by visiting [this link.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

* djawir Community will not sell, transmit or distribute any data held without your prior permission or consent, unless required to do so under relevant Indonesia legislation.

* All other information provided by you goes into a "public profile" and is entirely optional, all information held in that profile is held there at your own risk. This info is edited via your Account Panel in the forums.

* You have a legal right for the personal information held at djawir Community to be updated if it is incorrect or deleted if you choose. Most of this can be done through your Account Panel in the forums. If you are having issues with this, please Contact Us if you need help.

* djawir Community will take all reasonable effort to ensure that all personal information about you submitted is maintained secure on our server. However, we make no warranty to this.

* This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to check this page for updates or changes. If you have any questions regarding your privacy, then Contact Us
